Finding aid for University Herbarium (University of Michigan) Records, 1744-1745, 1851-1981, and 2001-2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Bartlett, Harley Harris, 1744-1855; 1875-1959
  - Correspondence and Associated Materials, 1875-1959
    - F
      - Furtado, C.X., 1936-1937 (Box 8)
    - G
      - Gabler, C.L.T., 1946 (Box 8)
        (S.W. Pacific)
      - Gager, C. Stuart, 1936 (Box 8)
        ("Botanic Gardens of the World")
      - Gail, Floyd W., 1936; 1946 (Box 8)
        (position at Univ. Idaho)
      - Gale, Eason M., 1950 (Box 8)
        (Chinese student aid see also Liu, Su-Ying)
      - Galler, S.R. (Box 8)
        (see U.S. Navy-0.N.R.)
      - Gambia, Secretary to Gov., 1951 (Box 8)
      - Gamboa, Melquides J., 1947-, fac.-U. Philippines (Box 8)
      - Gamma Alpha, 1938 (Box 8)
        (address)
      - Ganong, William F., 1930 (Box 8)
      - Gardner, Fletcher, 1938-1945 (Box 8)
        (linguistics see also: Philippines)
      - Gaskill, G.E. (Cornell Univ. Lib.), 1948 (Box 8)
        (bibliographies)
      - Gates, Frank C., 1919; 1945-1950 (Box 8)
        (see also Melchens, L.E.)
      - Gates, G.E. (Box 8)
      - Gates, R. Ruggles, 1915-1951 (Box 8)
      - Gault, Harry G., 1958 (Box 8)
      - Gauss, Robert F., 1926-1927 (Box 8)
        (1st Nat'l. Bank)
      - Geckler, Lucie Hodges, 1944 (Box 8)
      - General Rubber Company (Box 8)
        (see Rubber Investigation-Sumatra)
      - "Genetics", 1927-1943 (Box 8)
      - Gentle, Percy, 1931-1941 (Box 8)
        (plant collections, see Schufeldt, P.W.)
      - Gentry, Howard Scott, 1933-1964; 1939 (Box 8)
        (plant exploration-Hancock expedition of)
        (see also: McCulloch, I, Okkelberg, P., Guggenheim Found., Moe, H.A)
      - Ghani, A.R., 1957 (Box 8)
      - Gibson, R.A., 1948-1949 (Box 8)
        (Port Radium-O.N.R. Project)
      - Gier, L.J., 1945-1953 (Box 8)
      - Giesecke, Albert A., 1956 (Box 8)
      - Gifford, John P., 1945 (Box 8)
      - Gilbert, E.M., 1928 (Box 8)
      - Gilbert, William J., 1946 (Box 8)
      - Gilbert-Carter, Humphrey, 1924 (Box 8)
        (acidifying soil, exchange)
      - Gilkey, Helen M., 1948-1949 (Box 8)
        (Oenothera; Mrs. Clemens)
      - Gilly, Charles L., 1945 (Box 8)
        (Comparative Sci. Inst. of Antigua)
      - Gilmore, Melvin R., 1928-1929 (Box 8)
        (position/fellowship, see also Guggenheim-H.A. Moe)
      - Ginsburg, Norton S., 1955 (Box 8)
        (Fire & Prim.Agr.)
      - Glackin, William C., 1945 (Box 8)
      - "Gladys", 1926 (Box 8)
      - Glauser, Rudolph, 1946 (Box 8)
      - Gleason, Henry A., 1907-1939 (Box 8)
      - Glen Springs Trout Co., 1919 (Box 8)
      - Glezen, Carlisle S. & William H., 1945 (Box 8)
      - Gloyd, Howard K., 1936-1939 (Box 8)
      - Goddard, David R., 1944 (Box 8)
        (re Wildman, S.)
      - Goddard, Mrs. E.G., 1928 (Box 8)
        (?, Bailey lecture)
      - Goldthwait, J.W., 1911 (Box 8)
        (coastal subsidence)
      - Gonzales, Bienvenido M., 1947-1950 (Box 8)
        (Philippines., see also Philippines-J.R.H. Mem. Lib., Panlilio, F., & Santos, J.V.)
      - Goodman, George J., 1938-1947 (Box 8)
        (Gray Index; Lemnaceae)
      - Gordon, Neil E., 1938 (Box 8)
        (Phenanthrene symposium)
      - Gordon, Solon, 1940-1946 (Box 8)
      - Gordon, Winifred, 1946 (Box 9)
      - Gorgas Memorial Institute, 1940 (Box 9)
      - Gosline, William A., Jr. (Toledo Mus. Art), 1940 (Box 9)
        (1 letter from W.A.G., Jr.)
      - Gould, Frank W. (Box 9)
        (see Herbarium-Exchanges & Loans, Arizona)
      - Gould, J. W., 1959 (Box 9)
        (Sumatra)
      - Graber, Richard R. & Jean W., 1949 (Box 9)
        (students)
      - "Grace", etc., 1927 (Box 9)
      - Grace Line, 1945 (Box 9)
        (shipment of specimens)
      - Graham, Ralph G., 1955 (Box 9)
        (photographs)
      - Gram, Kai, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Gram, L.M., 1933 (Box 9)
        (space for Herbarium student)
      - Granick, Sam, 1938-1939 (Box 9)
      - Grant, D.K.S., 1956 (Box 9)
      - Grant, Marlin, 1957 (Box 9)
      - Grantham, James (Mae & Maureen), 1921-1940 (Box 9)
      - Grassl, Carl O., 1931-1959 (Box 9)
        (student & Darwin Mem. Exped.; photographic file)
      - Graves, Charles B., 1922-1924 (Box 9)
        (Prunus gravesii)
      - Graves, Ralph A., 1920 (Box 9)
        (National Geographic)
      - Gray Mem. Bot. Association (Box 9)
        (see Walp, R.L.)
      - Grayson, John F., 1956-, student (Box 9)
      - Greene, Albert E., 1929 (Box 9)
        (Iris)
      - Greene, Edward Lee, 1872-1914 (Box 9)
        (photographic file & Photograph)
      - Greene, E.L. "Landmarks...", 1919-1945 (Box 9)
      - Greene, Mrs. E.M., 1925 (Box 9)
      - Greene, John E., 1915-1916 (Box 9)
      - Greene, Roger S., 1945 (Box 9)
        (Harvard friend-education; see also Rockefeller Foundation)
      - Greenman, E.F., 1940 (Box 9)
        (Michigan Academy)
      - Greenman, Jesse M., 1920-1945 (Box 9)
        (nomenclature; specimens)
      - Greenway, P.J., 1956 (Box 9)
      - "Gretchen", student (Box 9)
      - Grey, Irving M., 1940 (Box 9)
        (publications)
      - Griffin, J.B., 1937-1944 (Box 9)
      - Grishko, N.N., 1944 (Box 9)
        (exchange)
      - Grisman, I., 1945 (Box 9)
      - Grodsky, V.A., 1940 (Box 9)
      - Groff, G. Weidman, 1951 (Box 9)
        (Lingnan Plant Exch, see also Liu, S.Y.)
      - Grosjean, G.M. (Box 9)
        (see Cram, Robert V.)
      - Grossman, Jos, 1944 (Box 9)
        (see Guggenheim-H.A. Moe)
      - Grosvenor, Gilbert, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
      - Grover, Frederick, 1932 (Box 9)
        (speak at Oberlin)
      - Grunder, Maynard S., 1945-1946 (Box 9)
      - Grundy, Sue, 1918 (Box 9)
      - Guayule, 1942-1947 (Box 9)
      - Guenther, F., 1937-1938 (Box 9)
        (see 12th Int. Hort. Congress)
      - Guerrero, Salvador, 1939 (Box 9)
      - Guggenheim Foundation-Mor, Henry A.; Mathias, James F., 1928-1951 (Box 9)
      - Guhl, Ernesto, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Guild, Stacy R., 1936 (Box 9)
      - Guimaraes Ferri, M., 1956 (Box 9)
      - Gunderson, G.K., 1945 (Box 9)
      - Gunther, Edmund E., 1930-, Gunther Gardens, Ypsi. State Hosp. (Box 9)
      - Gusindi, Father Martin, 1955 (Box 9)
      - Gustafson, A. H., 1932 (Box 9)
        (herbals)
      - Gustafson, F.G., 1921-1950 (Box 9)
      - Gustafsson, Ake, 1948 (Box 9)
        (Apomixis)
      - Guthe, Carl E., 1934-1937 (Box 9)
      - Guyer, Gordon, 1959 (Box 9)
        (words)
    - H
      - Haagen, C. (Box 9)
        (see Library-U of M)
      - Haas, Otto H., 1950 (Box 9)
        (Goethe)
      - Haberland, Wolfgang, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Habib, Nathan, 1940 (Box 9)
        (Bibliographies)
      - Haddon, Alfred C., 1934-1937 (Box 9)
        (Indonesia)
      - Haferkamp, Mary E., 1942-1946 (Box 9)
      - Hagerup, O., 1936 (Box 9)
        (Batak countries)
      - Hailman, H.F., 1945 (Box 9)
        (advice to beginning student)
      - Hain, M.A., 1956 (Box 9)
      - Haines, Mrs. E.O., 1946 (Box 9)
        (Amorphophallus Rivieri)
      - Haines, Harry C., 1955-1956 (Box 9)
      - Haiti-Chief of Police, 1941 (Box 9)
        (authorization)
      - Hale, William J., 1949 (Box 9)
        (cellulose degradation)
      - Hall, H.M. (Box 9)
        (see Herbarium-Collections-Univ. of Calif.)
      - Hall, Robert B. (Box 9)
        (see Philippines-J.R.H. Mem. Lib.)
      - Hallberg, Boone, 1950 (Box 9)
      - Hallock, H.G.C., 1928 (Box 9)
      - Halpern, Joel M., 1958 (Box 9)
      - Hambleton, Elizabeth, 1944-1956 (Box 9)
        (Malay-maps, dictionaries, etc.)
      - Hamel, Carel, 1926-1946 (Box 9)
        (plant collecting, see Alm, Ragnar, Rahmat, i;c Shellabear, W.G.)
      - Hamilton, Richard W., 1956 (Box 9)
      - Hamilton, Rodgers D., 1950 (Box 9)
      - Hand, Cadet H., 1945 (Box 9)
      - Hanes, Clarence R., 1934-1938 (Box 9)
        (plant identifications, Hanes' will, also A.G.B.)
      - Hanley, Kathleen, 1950 (Box 9)
        (personal-Kansas City, Mo.)
      - Hanna, Les A., 1932-1933 (Box 9)
      - Hanna, Margaret, 1939 (Box 9)
        (re W.H.Hobbs)
      - Hanna, M.R., 1957 (Box 9)
      - Hanscen" Vera (Mrs. C.J.), personal-relative-Montana (Box 9)
      - Hansen, Carl W., 1944 (Box 9)
      - Hansen, Ethel B., 1928-1946 (Box 9)
        (see also Cross, J.C., Kay, G.F., Shadle, A.R.)
      - Hansen, E.E., 1931-1932 (Box 9)
      - Hansen, Walter W., 1947 (Box 9)
      - Hardin, Mrs. Eleanor L., 1947 (Box 9)
      - Hardison, John R., 1941 (Box 9)
      - Hardy, Benson B., 1947 (Box 9)
      - Hardy, George A., 1949-1951 (Box 9)
      - Hargreaves, R.P., 1958 (Box 9)
      - Harker, Stanley, 1956 (Box 9)
        (invitation & reply)
      - Harland, J.P., 1922 (Box 9)
      - Harley, Mrs. George W., 1957 (Box 9)
        (directions for collecting palms)
      - Harley, Anifred J., 1957 (Box 9)
      - Harper, Robert A., 1927-1928 (Box 9)
        (Quercus sp. see also "Botanical Abstracts" & National Research Council Fellowships)
      - Harper, Roland M., 1907-1954 (Box 9)
        (photograph in Photograph Album)
      - Harris, Clyde, 1940 (Box 9)
        (Fairchild Garden)
      - Harris, John, 1956 (Box 9)
      - Harris, J. Arthur, 1925-1929 (Box 9)
      - Harris, Margwyn S., 1945 (Box 9)
      - Harris, Norman D., 1957 (Box 9)
        (Bailey-Philippine algae)
      - Harris, Tom M., 1930 (Box 9)
        (coal spores)
      - Harrison, Carrie, 1915-1918 (Box 9)
      - Harrison, Ethelwyn, 1928 (Box 9)
      - Harrison, J.R., 1945 (Box 9)
        (colchicine)
      - Harrix, G. Bryan, 1949 (Box 9)
        (collecting-Mexico)
      - Harroy, Jean Paul, 1955 (Box 9)
      - Harshberger, John W., portrait (Photograph Album) (Box 9)
      - Hartford Insurance, personal (Box 9)
      - Hartley, C.W.S., 1958-1959 (Box 9)
      - Hartog, Adrian, 1936 (Box 9)
        (Batak book)
      - Harvard University, 1935-1956 (Box 9)
      - Harvey, Benson H., 1938 (Box 9)
      - Harvey, LeRoy H., 1936-1947 (Box 9)
        (student-photograph)
      - Harvill, Alton M., 1941-1951 (Box 9)
        (student, see also J.P.Anderson)
      - Harwood, C.S., 1932 (Box 9)
        (plant specimens, see also Schipp, W.A.)
      - Haskell, Daniel C., 1940-1944 (Box 9)
      - Hasselbring, Heinrich, 1932 (Box 9)
      - Hasselbring, Reinhart, 1941 (Box 9)
      - Hatch, Carl A. (Box 9)
      - Hatch, J.E., 1932 (Box 9)
        (Nicaragua)
      - Hatheway, William H., 1951 (Box 9)
      - Hatt, Robert T., 1937-1952 (Box 9)
        (Cranbrook)
      - Havens, R.D., 1947 (Box 9)
      - Haverbeck, H.D.S., 1955 (Box 9)
      - Hawkes, Alex D., 1946 (Box 9)
        (collections-Cuba)
      - Hayden, James R., 1945 (Box 9)
        (Memorial)
      - Hayes, Stanley W., 1940 (Box 9)
        (Upness Arboretum)
      - Hayne, Don W., 1946 (Box 9)
      - Heater, Russell C., 1955 (Box 9)
        (Fire & Prim. Agr. (U.S.A.-Foreign Service))
      - Heath, W.L., 1949 (Box 9)
        (aid to Service Men (U.S.D.A.-Forest Prod.))
      - Heilbrunn, Lewis V., 1928; 1937 (Box 9)
        (staffing)
      - Heim, Roger, 1957 (Box 9)
      - Hein, Mason, 1956 (Box 9)
      - V. Heine-Geldern, Robert, 1937-1957 (Box 9)
        (ethnology-Sumatra)
      - Helbig, Karl, 1937 (Box 9)
      - Heller, Beverly, 1946 (Box 9)
      - Hemenway, Ansel F., 1936 (Box 9)
      - Henshall, J.A., 1910 (Box 9)
        (collection & identification)
      - Herb. Society of Amer., 1938-1939 (Box 9)
        (herbs & medicinal plants)
      - Herbarium: Collections, 1904-1954
        - Aiona, Isabella, algae, 1942 (Box 9)
        - Anning, Norman, 1925 (Box 9)
          (wild rose seeds)
        - Arnold Arboretum, 1939-1949 (Box 9)
        - Bank, Theodore P., Aleutian bryophytes, 1945 (Box 9)
        - Bartlett, H.H., 1904-1950; 4 folders (Box 9)
        - Bartlett Field Notes, 1926-1944; 2 folders (Box 10)
        - Beard, Pamela, 1945-1946 (Box 10)
        - Blair, Amy L. & Earl M. orchids, Sumatra, 1924-1926 (Box 10)
        - Blumer, J.C., 1910 (Box 10)
        - Broadway, W.E., 1927-1932 (Box 10)
        - Buch, Wilhelm, Port-au-Prince, 1946 (Box 10)
        - Buckholz, J.T., New Caledonia, 1947 (Box 10)
        - Burns, R.C., Parke-Davis, 1946 (Box 10)
        - California, University of Southern, M.S.Clemens, 1947 (Box 10)
        - Chand, T. Rup., det by C.K.Tseng, 1941 (Box 10)
        - Chanek, Mercedes, 1931 (Box 10)
        - Chile, University of, algae, 1946 (Box 10)
        - Clemens, Mary S., 1916-1942 (Box 10)
          (see also Clemens file)
        - Cole, Emma J., 1923-1938 (Box 10)
        - Collom, Mrs. Rose, Arizona plants, 1934-1938 (Box 10)
        - Conover, J. Towne, Okinawa, 1948 (Box 10)
        - Croker, Richard S., Japan, 1946 (Box 10)
        - Ebalo & Conklin Elmer, Adolph D.E. Farlow, 1939-1949 (Box 10)
        - Elmer, A.D.E., 1934-1956 (Box 10)
        - Finch, R. Gordon, 1933 (Box 10)
        - Fleming, R.L., 1932 (Box 10)
        - Gentle, Percy, 1931 (Box 10)
        - Gentry & Halberg, succulents, Oaxaca, 1950 (Box 10)
        - Grant, J.M., Northwest, 1929-1933 (Box 10)
        - Gressitt, J. Linsley, Formosa, Loochoos, 1934-1937 (Box 10)
        - Harper, Roland A., 1939 (Box 10)
        - Herter, W.G., Montevideo, 1947 (Box 10)
        - Holstvoogd, C., West Java, 1947 (Box 10)
        - Houghton, Douglass, 1913 (Box 10)
        - Hunziker, A.T., 1943 (Box 10)
          (plant specimen)
        - Jordal, Louis H., 1939 (Box 10)
          (also see reg. file,)
        - Koelz, Walter, 1930-1941 (Box 10)
        - Krueger, H.G.P., Mexicom, 1940 (Box 10)
        - Krukoff, Boris A., undated (Box 10)
          (see reg. file,)
        - Legett, J.H., Oenothera, 1913 (Box 10)
        - Lin, Lae Kwan, China, 1948-1949 (Box 10)
        - Liu, Y., China, undated (Box 10)
        - Llana, Alfredo, algae, Chile, 1945 (Box 10)
        - McCarroll, Dorothy, Peru, 1940 (Box 10)
        - McFarlin, James B., Florida, 1930 (Box 10)
        - Peterson, Frederick W., 1944 (Box 10)
        - Pewe, Troy L., Alaska, 1946 (Box 10)
        - Philippines, 1939 (Box 10)
        - Porter, Harold L., Iwo Jima -- Bonin, 1946 (Box 10)
        - Potter, David, Labrador, 1937 (Box 10)
        - Pringle, (University of Vermont), 1937-1938 (Box 10)
        - Rahmat, 1936-1938 (Box 10)
        - Rahmat-Field Notes, 1932-1936; 3 folders (Box 10)
        - Rahmat-Sumatran woods, undated (Box 10)
        - Reed, Ernest, 1939 (Box 10)
        - von Rozynski, H.W. Mexico, 1932 (Box 10)
        - Salvoza, F.M. Salvoza?, Philippines, 1934 (Box 10)
        - Schallert, Paul O., 1951 (Box 10)
        - Schipp, William A., 1929 (Box 10)
        - Schneck, Jacob, 1908 (Box 10)
        - Sleeper, David A., Alaska, 1949 (Box 10)
        - Spetzman, Louis, 1949 (Box 10)
        - Steere, R.L., Guam, 1945 (Box 10)
        - Steere, William C., 1933-1945 (Box 10)
        - Stork, Costa Rica, 1930 (Box 10)
        - Taam & Tsang, 1944-1945 (Box 10)
        - Taylor, W.R., 1946 (Box 10)
        - Tubbs, David O., 1932 (Box 10)
        - Warnstorf, New Hampshire, 1907 (Box 10)
        - Watson, Elba E., 1925 (Box 10)
        - Webster & Wilbur, 1950 (Box 10)
        - Weir, James R., Venezuela, 1940 (Box 10)
        - Yong-sok, O., 1951 (Box 10)
        - Zurich Botanical Gardens, New Caledonia, 1954 (Box 10)
        - Determinations, 1935-1945 (Box 10)
          (see also individual collectors)
      - Heribert-Nilsson, N., 1948 (Box 10)
      - Hermann, Barbara, 1947 (Box 10)
      - Hermann, Frederick J., 1922- (Box 10)
        (student, see also A.S.Pease, G.H., Smith, J.M., Sayles, photographic file)
      - Hernandes X., Efraim, 1946 (Box 10)
        (Mexican flora)
      - Hervey, E. (Box 10)
      - Heslop Harrison, J.W. (Box 10)
      - Hess, Alfred F. (Box 10)
      - Hess, Robert W., 1950 (Box 10)
        (Rubiaceae woods)
      - "Higher Education", L.E.Blauch ed., 1947 (Box 10)
      - Hildebrand, J.R., 1939-1940 (Box 10)
      - Hildebrandt, Dora (Mrs. T.H.) (Box 10)
      - Hill, Peter J.R., 1948-1950 (Box 10)
        (student-see also H.J.Coolidge,)
      - Hilton, M.S., 1945 (Box 10)
        (cascara; ideographs)
      - Hinsdale, Wilbert B., archaeology in Michigan (Box 10)
      - (State) Historical Soc. of Washington, 1924 (Box 10)
        (re Thomas A. Bruhin)
      - Hitchcock, Albert S., 1909-1933 (Box 10)
        (identifications; Code)
      - Hitchcock, Charles B., 1955-1957 (Box 10)
      - Hitchcock, C. Leo, 1944-1951 (Box 10)
        (Lycium; plant exchange)
      - Hobbs, Cecil, 1947-1958 (Box 10)
      - Hobbs, William H., 1921-1953 (Box 10)
      - Hodge, Walter H., 1949 (Box 10)
        (Palm Soc.; publication)
      - Hoffman, Olive, 1928 (Box 10)
        (Application)
      - Hoffmaster, Peter J., 1937 (Box 10)
        (CCC collecting-Michigan, see also Natural Areas)
      - Holch, A.E., 1932 (Box 10)
      - Holden, James S., 1955 (Box 10)
        (Detroit Zoo-labelling of plants)
      - Holdridge, Leslie R., 1939-1947 (Box 10)
        (student; see also R.H.Allee (photographic file))
      - Holland, Kenneth (Box 10)
        (U.S. Department of State, U.S. Department of State-Fulbright Funds)
      - Holloway, Ancil D., 1934 (Box 10)
        (Mexican oaks; see also A.C.Kinsey)
      - Holloway, Paul H., 1938 (Box 10)
        (knife)
      - Holman, Richard M., 1920 (Box 10)
      - Holstein, G.W., 1910 (Box 10)
      - Holt, Claire (Box 10)
        (see East Indies Institute)
      - Homer, Nils A., 1928 (Box 10)
      - Honey, Edwin E., 1932 (Box 10)
      - Hoogstraal, Harry, 1939-1942 (Box 10)
        (collector-Mexico)
      - Hoover, J.W., 1944 (Box 10)
        (Mindanao)
      - Hopkins, Milton, 1944 (Box 10)
      - Hopun, Lescadio E., 1931-1933 (Box 10)
        (British Honduras; Maya story)
      - Horn, Claud L., 1940 (Box 10)
      - Horowitz, S., 1944 (Box 10)
        (Buenos Aires)
      - Hotchkiss, H. Stuart (Box 10)
      - Hottes, Alfred C., 1932 (Box 10)
        (Better Homes Gardens, Bot. Gardens, U of M)
      - Hottes, Charles F., 1928 (Box 10)
        (positions)
      - Houghtaling, Helen (Kaltenborn), student (Box 10)
      - Houghton, Edwin W. (Box 10)
      - House, Homer D., 1920-1922 (Box 10)
        (Oenothera-N.Y.)
      - Houser, R.H., 1945 (Box 10)
      - Houston, Charles O., Jr., 1950 (Box 10)
      - Hovanitz, William, 1946-1954 (Box 10)
        (Russel Award; genetics; see Arctic Inst. of N.A.; Am. Philos. Soc.; N.R.C.-Fellowships)
      - Howard, Edward A., 1931 (Box 10)
        (cycads)
      - Howard, Margaret Bell, 1945 (Box 10)
      - Howard, Richard A., 1945 (Box 10)
        (A.F. collecting-fungi)
      - Howe, Marshall A., 1916 (Box 10)
      - Howe, M.D., 1945 (Box 10)
      - Hoy, W.E., 1951 (Box 10)
        (botanical survey)
      - Hu, Hsien-Hsu, 1927 (Box 10)
      - Hubbard, George D., 1929 (Box 10)
        (fossil coal)
      - Hubbard, Lucius L., 1921 (Box 10)
        (ethnology)
      - Hubbell, Theodore H., 1947 (Box 10)
        (fac.-U. Philippines, Allis Hussey)
      - Hubbs, Carl L., 1938-1949 (Box 10)
        (personnel)
      - Humbert, Henri, 1955-1958 (Box 10)
      - Hummel, Arthur W., 1947 (Box 10)
        (Arthur F. Wright, M.C. Wright)
      - Humphrey, Blanche, 1936 (Box 10)
      - Humphrey, Harry B., 1938 (Box 10)
        (wildrose)
      - Humphreys, W.R., 1929 (Box 10)
        (Dean-student "irregularity")
      - Hunt, Alma (Lavigne), 1940-1944 (Box 10)
      - Hunt, H.R., 1929 (Box 10)
        (epileptics)
      - Hunt, Marjorie, personal-A.A./Nebraska (Box 10)
      - Hunt, Mary (Mrs. Fred) (Box 10)
        (see Bartlett, Mary Alice)
      - Hunt, Mrs. Roy Arthur, 1949-1961 (Box 10)
        (Botanical books)
      - Hunter, Lillian M., 1940 (Box 10)
      - Huntley, Frank L., 1947 (Box 10)
        (Barbour Scholarships)
      - Hus, Henri (?) (Box 10)
      - Hussey, Allis F., 1945 (Box 10)
      - Huston, S. Arthur, 1921 (Box 10)
      - Hutchinson, John O., 1938-1939 (Box 10)
        (growing plants (plant specimen))
      - Hwanan College, 1948 (Box 10)
        (see also Wang, Lucy C.)
      - Hyde, Charles C., 1947 (Box 10)
        (fac.-U. Philippines
    - I
      - Ibanez, Jaime, 1945 (Box 10)
      - Icaza, Ernesto, 1941 (Box 11)
      - Ikabe, H., 1920 (Box 11)
        (biochemistry-Ford Motor Co.)
      - Iltis, Hugh H., 1950-1957 (Box 11)
        (palms, Fire & Prim. Agr.)
      - Ilustre, Frederico, 1947 (Box 11)
      - Indonesian correspondence, 1919-52, 1958 (Box 11)
        (undecipherable signatures)
      - Infantry Journal, 1945-1946 (Box 11)
      - Inglis, Elizabeth (Mrs. James), 1947-1952 (Box 11)
        (A.C.B.)
      - Ingram, Harry, 1938 (Box 11)
        (book)
      - Inman, Ondess L., 1938 (Box 11)
        (use of cyclotron)
      - Institute of Ethnic Affairs (Box 11)
        (see Collier, J.)
      - Institute of International Education (Box 11)
        (see also Midthun, L., Fisher, D.J.; Buell, Mrs. F.D.; Pavetti-Morin, C.)
      - Instructions to Naturalists in the Armed (Box 11)
        (see Jar-related-A.F. collecting Forces)
      - International Christian University, Japan (Box 11)
        (see Troyer, M.E.)
      - International Committee for Brid Preservation (Box 11)
        (see Pearson, T.G. International Education Board, see Shepardson, 7.H.)
      - de Irmay, Hernando, 1951; 1955 (Box 11)
      - Isbell, Franziska, 1951 (Box 11)
    - J
      - Jackson, William A., 1945 (Box 11)
        (linguistics; see also Library-Harvard Univ.)
      - Jacobs, Charlotte, 1944 (Box 11)
        (war effort)
      - Janaki-Ammal, 1928-1959 (Box 11)
      - Janson, Elsie, 1937 (Box 11)
      - Jao, Chin-Chih, 1946-1948 (Box 11)
        (algae)
      - Japan International Christian Univ. Foundation (Box 11)
      - Japanese Garden, Atlantic City. (Box 11)
        (see Rowley, Jessie L)
      - Jeffrey, E.C., 1909; 1922 (Box 11)
      - Jennings, Jesse D., 1951 (Box 11)
      - Jepson, Allis L., 1910; 1918 (Box 11)
      - Jereza, Agustin, 1947 (Box 11)
      - Jervis, Roy N., 1939-1956 (Box 11)
        (student; see also Vogt, F.H.)
      - "Joe", 1920 (Box 11)
        (cousin)
      - Johannessen, Carl, 1955-1958 (Box 11)
      - John, Charles A., 1946 (Box 11)
      - Johns, M. Rae, 1938 (Box 11)
        (Heliantheae)
      - Johnson, Albert G., 1954 (Box 11)
      - Johnson, A. Rex (Box 11)
        (see U.S.D.A.-Foreign Agri. Relations)
      - Johnson, Duncan S., 1929 (Box 11)
        (living plants)
      - Johnson, Herbert H., 1947 (Box 11)
        (Philippines; philately)
      - Johnson, Malcolm, 1956 (Box 11)
      - Johnston, Ivan M., 1938-1949 (Box 11)
      - Johnston, J.B., 1934 (Box 11)
      - Johnston, John R., 1908 (Box 11)
        (Cuba)
      - Jones, D.D. (Box 11)
        (see U.S.D.A.-For. Agr. Relations)
      - Jones, Fred R., 1920-1921 (Box 11)
      - Jones, J.E., 1944 (Box 11)
        (curupi)
      - Jones, Kenneth L., 1939-1955 (Box 11)
      - Jones, Lewis Ralph, 1919 (Box 11)
        (Jour. Agr. Res.)
      - Jones, Paul H., 1932-1947 (Box 11)
      - Jones, Philip M., 1928- (Box 11)
      - Jones, Volney, 1945-1946 (Box 11)
        (ethnobotany)
      - Jordal, Louis H., 1947-1951; 1976 (Box 11)
        (student-Alaska)
      - "Josephina", 1947 (Box 11)
        (Philippines-Columbia Univ.)
      - Jotter, Lois (Cutter), 1937-1945 (Box 11)
      - Just, Theodore, 1939-1950 (Box 11)
        (see also White, Stephen S.)
    - K
      - Kaeiser, Margaret (Box 11)
        (reprint request, 1 card)
      - Kahin, George McT., 1952 (Box 11)
        (Southeast Asian Studies)
      - Kahn, Reuben, 1956 (Box 11)
        (letter on retirement)
      - Kalter, Louis B., 1945 (Box 11)
      - Kambhu, M.L.J., 1955-1956 (Box 11)
      - Kaplan, Wilfred, 1948 (Box 11)
        ("Rights")
      - Karpinski, Joseph et al, 1945 (Box 11)
      - Karsian, Karl, 1945 (Box 11)
      - Katsuda, Ginjiro, 1940 (Box 11)